The authorities in Russia are
bracing themselves today
for mass protests against the trial
of former billionaire Yuri Komarov.
The case against Mr. Komarov
has caused widespread division
amongst the Russian public,
some of whom view his incarceration
as a political maneuver
orchestrated by this man,
defense minister candidate
Viktor Chagarin.
What do you want Viktor?
Why are you doing this?
What do you want to accomplish tomorrow?
I'm prepared to pay for my sins.
You should prepare yourself too.
Yuri,
let's be civil about this.
We were friends once...
...we could be again.
Just give me the file...
...and I'll hand your life back to you.
Forget this stupid trial.
I don't want my life back.
You think I'm going to
let you talk tomorrow?
No one is going to hear you!
I own everybody in that courtroom.
You don't own me.
Mike.
Chagarin's making a move on Komarov.
Shit. I'll see if we got local.
We are ready to get started.
Make the call.
You won't disappoint me?
Have I ever disappointed you?
Anton.
Alik, it's Viktor.
Yuri Komarov says hello...
It's time to grab him.
Yuri Komarov?
...and GOODBYE.
McClane.
Hey, Murph, how you doing?
Nice grouping, Grandpa.
Yeah, not bad.
Is that it?
Yep. We found him.
It's not good, John.
Hospital or morgue?
Worse.
When was the last time
you spoke to this kid?
It's been a while.
Maybe a few years, even.
Last time I saw him, it was pretty ugly.
Well, there's a few different
versions in there,
but my people are pretty sure he's
being held at a Moscow prison
awaiting sentencing.
What's he charged with?
It's a nasty sheet.
He'll be lucky to get life.
He can never get out of his own way.
He had a lot of problems.
He's still my kid.
I know.
But it's Russia. They do things
differently over there.
Me, too.
Good luck, Poppy.
Thanks, kid.
Welcome to John F. Kennedy
International Airport.
Dad, I wish you would let me go with you.
You would never be able to resist
the urge to tell me what
to do all the time.
This isn't your fault. You know?
I just
hoped that he'd figured his life out.
I got you something.
"Idiot's Travel Guide."
Perfect.
Thank you, baby.
I love you.
I love you, too.
See you soon.
Dad?
Just try,
try not to make an even
bigger mess of things.
Good luck.
I love you. See you soon.
I was told you had something to offer me?
You're looking for evidence
against Yuri Komarov?
Perhaps.
Put me in the courtroom with him...
...and I'll testify that Komarov
hired me to murder Anton.
Did he?
I'll testify under oath.
That's good enough, isn't it?
...Draganskiy courthouse?
You speak Russian?
How did I do?
Well, you asked for a large bag of hair
on the way to Taganskaya courthouse.
But I got it. I got it.
Good.
Traffic sucks here, too, huh?
Sex?
You want sex? Sexy clubs?
No. No sex.
It sucks, this traffic.
What is it? An accident?
No.
Garden Ring. Is bad.
Always traffic, always traffic.
You're American?
Yeah, American. New York.
The Big Apple.
♪ I want to wake up in that
city that never sleeps ♪
That's it.
Frank Sinatra. Chairman of the Board.
That's right.
The Chairman. Yeah.
You sing good.
♪ These little town blues
are melting away ♪
Yes, I sing.
I sing all the time.
Yeah.
♪ King of the hill Top of the world ♪
Huh?
Heap. "Top of the heap."
All right, all right. Taganskaya
courthouse, right there.
Two blocks.
You better walk, traffic
is bad. Really bad.
What do I owe you?
Hey, no money.
No money, you let me sing.
You let me sing.
You listen to my singing. No money.
Welcome to Moscow.
♪ That little town blues are melting away
♪ I'm gonna make a brand new start of it
♪ In old New York
...protests in central Moscow,
following a day of demonstrations
in Russia.
...face charges publically
for the first time.
Security is tight, as there have been
several attempts on Komarov's life
since he's been in prison.
Quiet!
Order in the courtroom!
Order!
Seal the doors!
Detonator.
But, sir... the drivers?
It's gonna be loud.
Hey!
Quick!
Come on, come on!
Come on now!
Come, come.
Come!
The cage.
Check the cage.
They are not here.
No kidding.
What's happening?
Take Komarov alive...
...kill the other one.
Yes.
Alik.
We need this file.
Put that on!
Who are you?
Your best friend.
Jack!
Dad?
Get out of the van!
What are you doing here?
Jack! Hey!
Jack!
Shit.
Komarov! Komarov!
Quick... get the truck!
Go home.
What the fuck do you think...? Jack!
You're out of your depth, John.
Jack! What are you doing?
No! No!
We need him alive!
Jack!
You're gonna shoot me?
You're gonna shoot your own father?
You shouldn't be here, John.
You shouldn't be here.
What are you doing?
Jack!
Whoa!
You're gonna fucking run over me?
You're only making it worse!
Jack.
Get out of the way!
Call a cop!
Reaper One? Reaper One from 6-1-0.
Who's got him? Clock's running. Foxy.
On the paper now. Box on.
Copy that. Box on.
- Okay, here we go.
6-1, Reaper, we read you. Go ahead.
Reaper, how are we looking?
Your guy is late.
His rate of progress is way off.
MET now plus 6 minutes.
MCC Reaper. MET now plus 6.
This is un-frigging-believable.
MCC Reaper. That's not how it works.
Something's off. I know this
guy. This doesn't happen.
MCC Reaper, 6-1 is in the hole. Stand by.
6-1, be advised, your window is closed.
Time on target is no-go.
I say again, TOT is no-go.
Reaper, this is real-world,
not exercise, do you copy?
No, sir, Moscow police will have
shut down the Garden Ring.
Reaper! He's no-go for extraction.
It's too late. Shut it down. Pull it!
6-1, mission window is closed.
Reaper is out of here.
Come on!
Shit!
Get me Operations.
Reaper!
Get Mike Collins looped in.
Tell him it's Plan B, safehouse. Go now!
Plan B. No choice.
Shit.
It's blown. They shut the Garden Ring.
Harvest is in effect. Keep on working.
Let's finish this, Foxy.
Damn you, McClane!
Damn you!
Oh, fuck!
Jack! I'm not done talking to you!
Who is this?
Come on, go!
Concentrate, please.
That's right, come on through, yeah!
See if you can hit this guy!
Jesus!
I'm tired of this guy.
RPG now!
Jesus!
You missed! Interesting choice, man.
Hey, hey!
Hey!
Whoa!
Hey! Whoa!
Come on!
You gotta be fucking kidding me!
What?
Do you think I understand
a word you're saying?
Jesus Christ.
It's okay, I'm fine, thanks.
Oh, man, you're driving like my grandma!
When I say drive, I mean fly!
Oh, yeah!
Get out of the way!
Oh, God.
Jesus!
Oh, for the love of...
Hi, honey.
- Dad? Can you hear me?
How is Moscow? Can I call you back?
Wait, don't...
Sorry, ma'am!
Sorry!
Did you see this guy?
Dad, can you hear me?
Dad, are you still there?
Dad?
Oh, man!
Knock knock.
You still there?
Yeah, I'm here.
So, how is Jack? Have you seen him?
Uh, yep, looking right at him.
Is he okay?
I haven't really caught up with
him yet, but he looks good.
I'm gonna have to call you back.
What's going on there?
Luce, can I call you right back?
Don't hang up...
Guess who!
I've had enough of this shit.
Oh, man, hey!
Is that it? Is that your best shot?
Damn you, John.
Damn you!
Hey! Up here!
Shoot up here!
John! Get in!
Get in before I change my mind. Jesus!
Take your time.
Jack, what the fuck was that, huh?
Shut up. Shut up, John.
I swear to God, I will put
a bullet in you this time.
Who do you think you're talking to?
The last person I want to see.
Well, maybe you missed the
whole part back there
where I saved you and Papa Geppetto here
from a whole bunch of Russian bad guys.
You saved? You saved?
That's right, saved.
Shut up. Shut up.
You're a world class screw-up,
you know that, John?
I'm a screw-up? I'm a screw-up?
I'm still your father.
Yeah, nothing I can do about that.
What a joke.
Just shut up. Try not to touch
anything, all right?
You've done enough goddamn damage.
The appointment is next week...
We will begin immediately.
Excuse me, sir. Komarov has escaped.
I'll call you back. There is
a problem with Komarov.
What happened?
Some sort of attack on the courthouse.
Who took him?
They don't know yet.
What do you mean you don't know?
Eh...
...well it's confusing...
Eyewitnesses say they saw Komarov...
...with an American.
What American?
John McClane.
Let's go.
After you.
Yeah, I got him. Okay, I'm on it.
Look, Mike, we had an unexpected
delay. I'm sorry.
I understand.
This is the last guy on earth
I expected to see.
Listen to me, Yuri, you have half
of Moscow looking for you.
I need you to get dressed. Why am I here?
Please put on these clothes. Trust me.
This is the key to your
cuffs. Take these.
Oh, my Jesus.
Are you okay? What?
Do you have the file on Chagarin?
This is what you been doing, Jack?
Spy shit?
This is it?
You're a spy? Oh, my God.
The 007 of Plainfield, New Jersey.
Very nice.
McClane, shut up.
Take it easy, Oddjob.
I'm on vacation.
Your mom will be pleased.
We thought you were doing
drugs or something.
Mr. Komarov.
Or selling drugs, but
that was me, really.
Do you have the file on Chagarin?
Yes, or no?
It's very simple, Yuri.
You give me the file, and
I get you out of Russia.
And you're a free man. What do you say?
It's not about me. I don't
care about my life.
Well, that's the deal.
It's the only deal.
Come on.
Come on, Yuri. Help yourself.
What's it gonna be?
Yes or no?
The clock is ticking, Yuri. Come on.
You will get me out of here?
Only the three of you?
Whoa, Nijinsky. I'm not in the gang.
I just got off the plane.
I'm still jet-lagged.
I'm not involved in this. Huh, Jack?
Only if I can take my daughter with me.
Chagarin's people will kill her.
Fine. Make it quick.
Ah.
Where's the file?
It's in a vault in Prypiat, but
the key is here in Moscow.
At Hotel Ukraina.
Make your call. We're going
to the Ukraina, let's go.
It's papa...
I'm fine, Sunshine...
...we'll talk later.
Listen.
I'll be waiting for you where your mother
and I shared our first dance.
Now.
Hurry! Hurry! You understand?
Mike, listen, I'm sorry about
this morning, man.
It's fine.
Okay, let's go.
Contact!
Down! Get down!
Go! Get down! Go, go, go!
John, cover!
Come on, buddy!
Go! Go!
That's right, jerk-off!
All right, let's move, John!
I'm on fucking vacation!
Come on, time to hustle. Watch your head.
McClane, move it.
8,000 fucking miles for this?
Get down, Yuri. Stay low!
Head down.
Come on. Go, go!
Safe house, my ass.
He knows how old we are, no?
Come on.
Here, here, here.
Sit down. You're all right.
Let me look at you.
It's all right. You're fine.
What are you doing?
Jack.
Calm down, Yuri, okay? You're
gonna be just fine.
Here, put this on, stay warm.
What was that, John? Five
minutes? Five minutes?
You blew a three-year op in five minutes!
You're welcome! What do
you want me to do?
Unbelievable.
I'm so fucking burned. I got no
friends in this town anymore.
What about your people at Langley?
Just give them a call.
Give me your phone.
It's a two-year contract on that phone.
What are you carrying? Give me that.
All right. You got any cash on you?
Some American money.
What are you talking about?
We need to keep on moving.
We have to get this guy to a doctor.
To medical attention, Jack.
The mission stands.
Your mission is bleeding out over there.
The mission continues.
We go to the hotel.
Come on, let's move. Let's move.
This is nuts.
What, are you going to go out
and kill somebody else now?
Why all this trouble for just one guy?
He's a political prisoner.
Not that you care, John,
but it's a matter of national
security, all right?
He's got the goods to stop Viktor Chagarin,
and we need that to happen.
Well, great, Jack.
Let's drop him off at the Embassy,
and we can go home.
Are you kidding me? After what
happened at the safe house?
Look, it doesn't work
like that, all right?
It's a huge diplomatic mess,
and I'm a burnable asset.
So, I now need that file
to un-fuck this mission.
Any more questions?
Yeah, just one.
How come you never called and
told me where you were?
Like you'd give a shit.
All right, hold up, hold up.
Okay, Yuri, listen to me, all
right? We're almost done.
As soon as we get that key,
we're gonna grab the file,
get you and your daughter
out of Russia, all right?
All right.
Listen to me, you're doing
good. All right?
I need you to hang here a second.
Keep an eye on him, John.
Hey, hey.
What is it with all this "John" shit?
Whatever happened to "Dad?"
Good question.
In Russia, we have word for men like him.
"Krutoi."
It means "tough," "hard."
In America, it means "juvenile
delinquent."
Is he your only child?
No. I got a daughter, too.
You?
I have only my Solnyschka.
When she was little, I was
working all the time.
I believed work was all that mattered.
I screwed my kid's life up, too.
You work all the time
around the clock most of the
time, when you're a cop.
I just thought that working all the
time was a good thing, you know?
I didn't help him at all.
It's never too late,
I hope.
Okay, let's go.
All right, Yuri, which part of the
building is the ballroom in?
Main tower.
Main tower. Which floor?
Top floor.
What about security?
You remember any guards? Cameras?
Anything like that?
I don't know.
Well, I need you to remember.
I was in prison for five years,
how should I know?
Everything could have changed. I know.
Just think, all right? Picture
it in your head.
The ballroom was closed in '89.
I think it's under construction now.
So that floor's unsecured.
I don't know! Listen! My
daughter is in there.
I'm scared to death, let's go!
Just calm down, Yuri.
I guess you have done that before.
Smart.
I could have done it.
Irina?
Papa.
Irina. Papa!
That's tender.
Really? I wouldn't know.
Need a hug?
We're not really a hugging family.
That's right.
We just have to get one thing...
...and then we're leaving
Moscow for good.
OK?
OK.
Who are they?
The young one works for CIA.
The old one is his father. Americans.
Then thank God for them.
There's something no good about this.
Just shut up, all right?
I'm telling you, Jack,
this smells bad.
Just stop, okay?
This might seem like a totally
foreign concept, you know?
I know you love to just
run in, making shit up.
But like any professional, I have a plan.
So let's just stick to it, okay?
Just move your plan along.
All right, Yuri, come on. Let's
grab the key, get out of here.
Yes.
Just take a moment.
How you doing?
Fine.
How did you get over here so quick?
Well...
I took Garden Ring.
Oh, the Garden Ring. Supposed
to always be bad, right?
Hey, John.
Did you get stuck in traffic?
I have it! I have it.
Welcome, Americans.
Put your goddamn guns down, asshole!
Papa, what is going on?
Give me your weapons.
Come and get them.
Really?
Really.
Papa.
Yuri.
Do it.
I thought you were a problem child.
This a part of your plan,
Mr. Professional?
What are you doing?
It's about money, papa...
...millions of dollars.
You think life was easy for me?
While you were sitting in
prison being a victim?
But,
I'm your father.
And I am your daughter.
We should kill the old man now.
We still need him.
But them you can kill.
Thank you.
Hi.
I don't know if I'm saying this right.
Do you know what I hate
about the Americans?
Everything.
Especially cowboys.
I could have been a dancer.
I swear to God.
But nobody supported me.
You two
have been such a
pain in the ass!
I prefer dancing, really.
But killing is much, much better
than working in a grocery shop!
Jesus Christ!
Nice one.
You guys. So arrogant.
It's not 1986, you know.
Reagan is dead.
Sorry. Oh, God.
What's funny there?
Can't tell you.
It's not you. I love these outfits.
You guys are looking good.
That was enough, thank you.
Let's dance.
Come on! Come on!
Jack!
Remember the last time we talked
just before you went away?
Oh, no! No, no!
You're not gonna open up to
me right before we die!
No, that's not your thing, John.
What's my thing?
Fucking killing bad guys,
that's your thing!
You're not gonna die today!
Go!
Shit!
Fuck.
We're finished, John.
I can't believe this.
This is unbelievable.
Jack. Hey!
Jesus!
Come on!
Let's get out of this building!
Where are they?
Come on.
Alik, that's it. We're done!
Let's go!
Break left!
Copy, Commander.
Do you have him?
Yes.
And the file?
Does he have it?
I need that file, Alik.
He's taking us to it.
No more mistakes, Alik.
And when you have the file...
...kill them both.
Yes, sir.
Shit.
That was exciting.
Yeah. Loads of fun.
You wanna go again?
Are you shot?
No.
No, I'm fine.
Let me take a look at that.
It's fine.
Oh, fuck.
I can't believe she betrayed
her father for Chagarin.
I don't understand that.
Someday you will.
Kids.
What's our next move?
I don't know.
You don't know? I don't know, all right?
I mean, I'm out of moves. I don't know.
I don't know.
I screwed up.
I blew the mission.
Well, then we're done, right?
Yeah, we're done.
We're done.
We should just go home.
We'll stop by a little pharmacy
on our way out of Moscow,
get you some Merthiolate or mercury
and fix up your little scratches, here.
Get you home. Get a little toy set.
Get yourself a nice warm glass of
milk with a little Bosco in it.
Get your CIA slippers.
All right.
What? I get it.
What the hell are we gonna do?
What's in the file?
Evidence on Chagarin.
Evidence about what?
Chernobyl.
Look, listen to me.
Komarov and Chagarin used to have this
nasty little side-racket going
on back in the day.
They siphoned weapons-grade
uranium, got greedy,
caused the meltdown.
Then, you know, they fell out.
Former partners, bad break-up.
Scumbags.
So, Chagarin had Komarov thrown in jail.
You know, put him in a hole,
forget about him.
Doesn't have to worry anymore.
So what happened to rescuesque?
Well, he grew a conscience.
Yeah, well, that figures.
Listen, Chagarin is bad news.
He's the real deal.
If we see this guy in control, we're gonna
see the whole thing fall apart.
I'm talking terrorism,
WMDs,
nukes.
Someone has to stop him.
Well, that's what we do.
We go out to Chiapep and we do our thing.
Our thing?
Yeah.
We go out there and kill
a lot of scumbags.
What? You got something better to do?
All right. Pull it.
You're not gonna cry, are you?
Just pull it.
Everybody needs a good cry
once in a while, Jack.
Don't be ashamed. Pull it.
You remember that time when
you and Ralphie Mauser were gonna
have that house-painting job?
Got your finger caught in the ladder,
you cried for about five, six days.
John, just pull it!
All right.
On three. Here you go.
One, two...
Good God.
Jesus.
When was the last time you
had a tetanus shot?
You all right?
Yeah.
We need a car.
Atta boy.
Back to work.
Hey, Watergate, how's that lock coming?
Almost there.
Here, try these.
Come on.
Oh, stealing. That's nice.
Real nice, John.
Yeah, I'm up for the Father
of the Year award.
Whoa.
All right.
How'd you know all of these
guns were gonna be here?
It's a Chechen hangout.
Owner doesn't like guns in the club,
so these bozos leave them in their cars.
You learn a lot in three years.
Yeah.
Are we really going to Chernobyl?
The Chernobyl.
The radioactive joint? Meltdown?
That's the one.
It's not the Chernobyl
in Switzerland, right?
With all the skiing and the
snow and everything?
You mean Grenoble?
No, sorry, we're not going to Grenoble.
Eddie Collins's kid took him
on vacation last year.
They went down to Boca.
Oh, yeah?
Spent four days at the track.
Well, that's nice.
That's relaxing.
Oh, yeah. Sure.
We have to go to Chernobyl?
Yeah, sorry about that.
But all the radioactive
stuff is out, right?
Is it as you remember, papa?
I don't want to remember.
Tough.
The file...
...is in the inner vault.
Very touching. Let's move.
Which one is it?
Get moving, old goat.
Couple of fresh coats of paint and
a weedwacker and it's good to go.
You know, at first, they denied
anything even happened.
Held a children's parade the
next day to prove it.
24 hours later, 50,000 residents
were evacuated.
Never came back.
As soon as they get in that vault,
Komarov's a dead man.
All right.
You got a plan?
Not really.
I kind of thought we'd just wing it.
You know, run in, guns blazing,
making shit up as we go.
Yeah? Yeah.
What is this? A pirate gun?
Yeah. It's old school, man.
Like you, right?
Yeah, like me.
One of these days, I'm gonna
have a long talk with you.
Look, Jack,
I'm sorry your partner got killed.
I'm sorry I fucked up your
day. That wasn't my plan.
I caused you problems.
You know, I came here for something else.
And all that other bullshit. I mean,
I had a pretty good day.
It's fun, running around with you.
It's good to see you.
I love you, boy.
You, too.
I want you to know I got your back.
I got yours, too.
All right. Let's go kill
some motherfuckers.
Key.
Okay, what the fuck is this?
I'm losing my patience. The fucking
file better be here.
Radiation has been pooling
in this room for decades.
You've underestimated us, Daddy dearest.
Bring it in!
Atta boy.
Come on! Come on!
Compound 27-4. It neutralizes
radiation, trust me.
What's this remind you of?
Newark.
All clear. We can ditch the suits.
The hell is that?
One billion euros worth
of enriched uranium.
What?
Don't worry, it's stable in this form.
File!
Irina, cut the crap, please.
No one here is speaking about
uranium. Where's the file?
No more games, where is the file?
That's no longer your concern.
Sunshine...
...you did well.
I told you...
...everything would work out.
Come to papa.
Pap, you're a genius.
I know.
Load it up.
Pegasus?
Do you copy?
A lot of hardware for a file.
Wheels up in five minutes.
Perfect.
Here you go, sir.
Team extraction completed.
She's all yours.
Good.
Are you inside?
Yes, yes, Viktor.
I'm inside.
Yuri?
You surprised?
I'm in the same place where
it all started...
...before you betrayed me.
Remember...
...you promised to give me my life back.
You gave it back to me.
I thank you for that.
And now...
...I'm going to take yours.
Static 4, we are ready for take off.
Static 4, do you copy?
Yuri!
Yuri.
Where's the dancer?
You okay? You hurt?
No.
I'm good.
I'm all right.
What's in these boxes?
Thank God you're here, Jack.
We have to leave.
They're coming back any minute.
Just let me get the file.
What's in the boxes?
It's U-235.
Weapons-grade uranium.
Armored cases.
The bomb kind?
Yeah, the bomb kind.
Not so fast, Eddie.
Are you crazy?
Yeah, a little bit.
I'm getting the file.
No. No, you're not.
The key. It's your vault, isn't it, Yuri?
What? No. No, I...
You put this shit in here, right?
What? No.
Right?
I didn't know, Jack.
Is that the dancer down there?
What are you talking about?
That's a tough break for a good athlete.
Jack, you know me.
Yeah, I know you. I know you.
I know him better.
Never was a file, was there, Yuri?
Of course there was no file.
It was simply bait.
What I needed was in this vault.
Chagarin was the only one with enough
power and influence to
get me out of jail.
I used him.
I used you.
It's about money.
When's it not about money?
You want to arrest me?
You're out of your jurisdiction,
Detective McClane, aren't you?
I wouldn't worry too much
about being arrested.
See, my boy
is in the CIA.
No phone call.
Spy shit.
Goddamn Americans. You
think you're so smart.
No, I'm not that smart.
I'm just on vacation.
My boy here,
he gonna put a whooping on you.
Move!
You can say goodbye to your
daughter, you dumbwit fuck.
Where's your little Soltschanitsa?
Shit! God damn it!
Shit!
Irina, I'm going to the roof...
The roof!
Jack!
Set at 91.
Power plant?
All good to go.
Let's go!
Subtle.
What the hell is in those
goddamn grenades?
Go get him!
I'm going to the helicopter!
Vadim, watch the tail.
Copy. You are at 120 meters...
...115 meters...
There is small arms fire
coming from the roof.
We have a guest.
Watch the tail for me there.
Come on!
Come on, hurry!
Vadim, give me firing control now...
Engaging!
Jack!
Shoot him!
With pleasure, papa.
I'm on fucking vacation!
Vadim! He is there! I see him!
The shit we do for our kids.
Yippee ki-yay, motherfucker.
What happened?
CG's shifted...
I've got full forward cyclic.
I can't hold it.
Jesus Christ!
Well done,
Mr. Super-spy.
What a shame your father won't
be alive to see you promoted.
Neither will you.
Hey! Jack!
Hang on, John!
John!
Come on!
We're out of ammunition!
Shit.
Bastards.
What the hell are you doing?
This is for you, papa.
John!
Dad!
Right here.
Did you just call me Dad?
No.
I didn't think so.
You're hearing things.
You got swimmer's ear.
We're not gonna grow any third
arms or anything, are we?
No.
You might lose your hair.
Laugh it up, kid.
This is you, five years from now.
It's rainwater. You'll be fine.
Besides, it's hard to kill a McClane.
Now you're a McClane?
Yeah, I'm a McClane. John McClane.
John McClane Junior.
Well, that makes you a "senior."
That's right.
Try not to forget it.
I'm your father.
Have some respect for your father.
Let me ask you something.
Do you go looking for trouble
or does it always just seem to find you?
You know, after all these years,
I still ask myself the same question.
♪ I had a dream last night That
I was piloting a plane
♪ And all the passengers
were drunk and insane
♪ I crash landed in a Louisiana swamp
♪ Shot up a horde of zombies
But I come out on top
♪ What's it all about?
♪ Guess it just reflects my mood
♪ Sitting in the dirt
Feeling kind of hurt
♪ All I hear is doom and gloom
♪ And all is darkness
♪ In my room
♪ Through the light, your face I see
♪ Baby, take a chance Baby,
won't you dance with me
♪ Lost all that treasure
in an overseas war
♪ It just goes to show you don't
get what you paid for
♪ Battle to the rich and
you worry about the poor
♪ Put my feet up on the couch
And lock all the doors
♪ What's that funky noise?
♪ It's the tightening of the screws
♪ Sitting in the dirt
Feeling kind of hurt
♪ All I hear is doom and gloom
♪ But when those drums
♪ Go boom, boom, boom
♪ Through the night
♪ Your face I see
♪ Baby, take a chance Baby,
won't you dance with me
♪ Yeah!
♪ Baby, won't you dance with me
♪ Ah, yeah
♪ Fracking deep for oil But
there's nothing in the sump
♪ There's kids all picking
at the garbage dump
♪ I am running out of water
so I better prime the pump
♪ I am trying to stay sober
but I end up drunk
♪ We'll be eating dirt Living
on the side of the road
♪ There's some food for thought
♪ Kind of makes your head explode
♪ Feeling kind of hurt
♪ Yeah!
♪ But all I hear
♪ Is doom and gloom
♪ And all is darkness
♪ In my room
♪ Through the night
♪ Your face I see
♪ Baby, take a chance
♪ Won't you dance with me
♪ Yeah!
♪ Come on!
♪ Baby, won't you dance with me
♪ I'm feeling kind of hurt
♪ Oh, yeah!
♪ Sitting in the dirt
♪ Baby, won't you dance with me ♪